A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1953-2004
Library of Virginia
- I. Commissioner's Correspondence, 1982-2004 (bulk 1995-2003)., Extent: 60 cubic feet (60 boxes). (Box 1-60)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1996 (bulk 1992-1993)
    - Kenaf Project on Eastern Shore (Box 55)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau (Box 55)
    - Reconstitution of World Trade Council (Box 55)
    - Federal Manual for Identi. And Delin. Juris. Wetlands (Box 55)
    - MOU - Initiative on Child Abuse and Neglect (Box 55)
    - Task Force on Cooperation with Land Grant Univ. (Box 55)
    - 1992-93 Budget Development (Schedule, etc.) (Box 55)
    - Food Safety Campaign (1992) (Box 55)
    - Veterinary Medical Advisory Committee (Box 55)
    - Animal Health Issues/Projects (Box 55)
    - Signed Trust Fund/Grants/Agreements (Box 55)
    - VDACS - Budget Addenda and Governor's Downsizing Prop. (Box 55)
    - 1 April 1992, Wine Research (Box 55)
    - Canola - An Exciting New Crop (D. Brann) (Box 55)
    - National Agriculture Marketing Association (Box 55)
    - Beneficial Insect Rearing Facility/Lyons (Box 55)
    - 1992 Ideas for State Fair/Susan K. Simpson (Box 55)
    - Robin R. Nelson/Mr. Odato's Complaint - Bon Air (Box 55)
    - Carrington Williams' USA/FSU Plan (Box 55)
    - Residential Pesticide Use Briefing (Box 55)
    - Raw Milk Sales Background Paper (Goat) (Box 55)
    - Responses to Animal Health and Other Advisory Comm. (Box 55)
    - Moving and Relocation Expenses for Hirees (Box 55)
    - Travel (Box 55)
    - Expense Vouchers (CVT) FY 92/93 (Box 55)
    - Turner's Travel Expenses (Box 55)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998
    - 1996-1998 Budget Development (Box 56)
    - 1996-1998 Budget Development (Box 56)
    - 1996-1998 Budget Biennium (Box 56)
    - 1996-1998 Budget Development (Box 56)
    - 1996-1998 Budget Development (Box 56)
    - Budget - Goals, Objectives and Strategies (Box 56)
    - USLGE (Box 56)
    - Summary of 1998 General Assembly Budget and Legislative Actions (Box 56)
    - 1998-2000 Budget Guidelines (Box 56)
    - 1998-2000 Budget Proposals (Box 56)
    - 1998 Legislative Proposals (Box 56)
    - Agriculture - Budget (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous, 1998-2004
    - 2004-06 Budget Addenda Request (Box 57)
    - 2004-06 Biennium Budget Instructions (Box 57)
    - 2004 Legislative Guidelines-Proposals (Box 57)
    - 2004-06 Governor's Budget Proposal (Box 57)
    - 1998-2000 Budget Performance Measures (Box 57)
    - Drought Response Tac (Box 57)
    - Common Ground: Forum on the Future of Southeast Virginia Agriculture (Box 57)
    - S.E. Virginia Farmers Market (Box 57)
    - National Transition Plan for Tobacco (Box 57)
    - Virginia Water Supply Initiative, E.O. 39 (Box 57)
    - Animal Industry Services, 1998-2000 Budget Issues (Box 57)
    - 2001-02 Operating Budget (Box 57)
    - 2000-2001 Operating Budget (Box 57)
    - Budget FY 2002 (Box 57)
    - 1998 Strategic Planning (Box 57)
    - 2000-2002 Strategic Planning (Box 57)
    - 1996-1998 Biennium Budget Development (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-2004
    - 1995 Budget (Box 58)
    - 1998-99 Operating Budget (Box 58)
    - FY 97-98 Operating Budget (Box 58)
    - FY 96 Operating Budget (Box 58)
    - Budget Reduction 2002-04 - Revisions After Veto Session (Box 58)
    - 2004 Legislative Session (Box 58)
    - 2003 Budget Reduction (Box 58)
    - 2000-2002 Budget Initiatives (Box 58)
    - Budget, 2003 (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous, 1996-2004
    - 1997 Budget Amendments (Box 59)
    - 1999 Budget Submissions (Box 59)
    - 2001 General Assembly Proposed Budget Amendments (Box 59)
    - 2002-2004 Budget (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - 1999-2000 Operating Budget (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - 2000-02 Budget Reductions (Box 59)
    - 2000-2002 Biennial Budget (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 59)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1996
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - FY95-96 Operating Budget (Box 60)
    - Budget (Box 60)
    - 1994-1996 Budget Reductions (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - 1994-1996 Biennium Budget Reductions (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Budget Reductions - Divisions (Box 60)
    - Division of Animal Health Budget (Box 60)
    - 1995 Budget Amendment Process (1) (Box 60)
    - 1995 Budget Amendment Process (2) (Box 60)
    - 1994-96 Budget (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - Not Labeled (Budget) (Box 60)
    - 1994-95 Operating Budget (Box 60)
    - 1991-92 Budget (Box 60)
- II. Commissioner's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1995-2003., Extent: 37 cubic feet (37 boxes). (Box 61-97)
  This series is arranged chronologically and documents the subjects addressed by the Commissioner's Office The subjects in this series overlap with the Commissioner's Correspondence series. Researchers should check both series. Notable subjects/correspondence include: National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA), Southern Association of State Departments of Agriculture (SASDA), Southern United States Trade Association (SUSTA), United States Department of Agricultre, United States Food and Drug Administration, Eastern Shore Vegetable and Shellfish Advisory Committee, Southern Dairy Compact, pesticides, budget, disasters, tobacco, and the Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission. The series consists of agendas, agreements, budgets, correspondence, executive orders, legislation memorandum, meeting notes, notes, presentations, and reports.
  - 1995
    - SASDA (Box 61)
    - SUSTA (Box 61)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 61)
    - Secretary of Education (Box 61)
    - EEO Committee (Box 61)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (Box 61)
    - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (Box 61)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - U.S. Dept. of Environmental Quality (Box 61)
    - Council on the Environment (Box 61)
    - Executive Orders (Box 61)
    - State Fair (Box 61)
    - Farm Bill, 1995 (Box 61)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 61)
    - Federal Mandates (Box 61)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 61)
    - Food Lion (Box 61)
    - Food Distribution (Box 61)
    - Forestry, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 61)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Gilliam, Glen (Box 61)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Dept. (Box 61)
    - Governor's Office (Box 61)
    - Grievance Procedures - Employee (Box 61)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Virginia Horse Center (Box 61)
    - Virginia Horse Council (Box 61)
    - House of Representatives (US Congress) (Box 61)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 61)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Information Technology Advisory Group (Box 61)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 61)
    - James City County Growers Cooperative (Box 61)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) (Box 61)
    - Jumet, Charles (NAFTA) (Box 61)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 61)
    - Laboratory Testing Services (Box 61)
    - Land Use (Box 61)
    - State Land Evaluation and Advisory Council (SLEAC) (Box 61)
    - Legislative Automated Systems, Division (Box 61)
    - Legislative Services, Division of (Box 61)
    - Legislative Session, 1995 (Box 62)
    - Legislation (Box 62)
    - Lynchburg Regional Diagn. Lab (Box 62)
    - Virginia Liaison Office (Box 62)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 62)
    - Mandates for State Agencies (Box 62)
    - Virginia Milk Commission (Box 62)
    - Minor Crops (Box 62)
    - Minority Business Enterprises, Dept. of (Box 62)
    - Virginia Dept. of Motor Vehicles (Box 62)
    - NAFTA (Box 62)
    - NAFTA Reservations (Box 62)
    - Nicotine (Box 62)
    - "Virginia's Open for Agribusiness" (Box 62)
    - Opportunity Virginia (Box 62)
    - Organic Operations Certification Manual (Box 62)
    - Oxygenated Fuel (Box 62)
    - Oxygenated Fuel Regulation (Box 62)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 62)
    - 1995 Pesticide Disposal Program - Contingency Plan (Box 62)
    - Pesticide Record Keeping (Box 62)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 62)
    - Plastic Pesticide Container Recycling Program (Box 62)
    - Potato Blight (Box 62)
    - Prompt Payment (Box 62)
    - Pseudorabies (Box 62)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 62)
    - Virginia Retirement System (Box 62)
    - Right to Farm (Box 62)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) (Box 62)
    - Savings Bond - 1995 (Box 62)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 62)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources (Box 62)
    - International Marketing, Office of (Box 62)
    - Agency Accomplishments (Box 62)
    - Accomplishments, 1993-1994 (Box 62)
    - Department of Accounts (Box 62)
    - Agendas, SMT (Box 62)
    - AG Commodities (Box 62)
    - AG News Releases (Box 62)
    - Agriculture Celebration, 1996 (Box 62)
    - AG Stewardship Act (Box 62)
    - Appointees (Box 62)
    - Virginia Apple Board (Box 62)
    - Aquaculture Plan (Box 62)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 62)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 62)
    - Audits - VDACS (Box 63)
    - Audits - Commodity Boards (Box 63)
    - APA Audit Work Plan (Box 63)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 63)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 63)
    - VDACS Award Committee (Box 63)
    - Biodiesel (Box 63)
    - Blanket Approvals - Travel (Box 63)
    - Boll Weevil (Box 63)
    - Brochures (Box 63)
    - Budget Amendments (Box 63)
    - 1996-1998 Biennium Budget Development (Box 63)
    - Virginia Cattlemen's Association (Box 63)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 63)
    - Clean Water Act (Box 63)
    - Virginia Code Commission (Box 63)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 63)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 63)
    - Community Work Expansion Program (Box 63)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 63)
    - Conflict of Interest (Box 63)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 63)
    - Consolidated Farm Service Agency (Box 63)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, Division of (Box 63)
    - Virginia Corn Growers Association (Box 63)
    - Crop Insurance (Box 63)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association (Box 63)
    - Deer Farming (Box 63)
    - House of Delegates (Box 63)
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry (Box 63)
    - Federal Disaster Assistance (Box 63)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 63)
    - Eastern Shore Marketing Cooperative (Box 63)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (Box 63)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 63)
    - Division of Marketing (Box 64)
    - Commodity Services (Box 64)
    - Foreign Office Travel Exceptions (Box 64)
    - International Marketing (Box 64)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 1995-96 (Box 64)
    - Dept. of Accounts (Box 64)
    - Aquaculture (Box 64)
    - AG in the Classroom (Box 64)
    - Agendas, SMT (Box 64)
    - AG News Release (Box 64)
    - AG Stewardship Act (Box 64)
    - Virginia Agricultural Sustainability Leadership Council (Box 64)
    - AG Week (Box 64)
    - Apiary Program (Box 64)
    - Virginia Apple Board (Box 64)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of (Box 64)
    - Virginia Apple Growers Association (Box 64)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition (Box 64)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 64)
    - Audits - Commodity Boards (Box 64)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 64)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 64)
    - VDACS Awards Committee (Box 64)
    - Virginia Biotechnology Research Act (Box 64)
    - Blanket Approvals - Travel (Box 64)
    - Boll Weevil (Box 64)
    - Brochures (Box 64)
    - Budget Amendments (Box 64)
    - Virginia Cattlemen's Association (Box 64)
    - Virginia Code Commission (Box 64)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 64)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 64)
    - Commonwealth Competition Council (Box 64)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 64)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 64)
    - Consolidated Lab Services, Dept. of (Box 64)
    - Virginia Corn Growers Association (Box 64)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association (Box 64)
    - Dairy Marketing Prices, Carolina, Virginia (Box 64)
    - Delegates (Box 64)
    - Spruill, C. Kermit (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous - Product and Industry Regulation (Box 65)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 65)
    - State Certified Seed Board (Box 65)
    - Senators (Box 65)
    - Sheep Referendum (Box 65)
    - Virginia Small Grains Board (Box 65)
    - Smokey Mountain Secrets (Virginia State Police) (Box 65)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 65)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Transfer (Box 65)
    - Sole Source (Box 65)
    - Southern States Cooperative (Box 65)
    - Southside Virginia Produce Cooperative (Box 65)
    - Southwest Farmers Market (Box 65)
    - Soy Ink (Box 65)
    - Space (Box 65)
    - Virginia Riparian Forest Buffer Task Force (Box 65)
    - Virginia State University (Box 65)
    - Strategic Planning Process Reports (Box 65)
    - Strategic Planning (Box 65)
    - Biotechnology Task Force (Box 65)
    - Food Safety Task Force (Box 65)
    - Task Force on Laboratory Services (Box 65)
    - Task Force on Cooperation with Land Grant Universities (Box 65)
    - Livestock Disposal Task Force (Box 65)
    - Tobacco (Box 65)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 65)
    - Treasury, Dept. of (Box 65)
    - Ukrop's (Box 65)
    - USDA (2) (Box 65)
    - USDA (1) (Box 65)
    - Workforce Transition Act (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 66)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council (Box 66)
    - Virginia State Apple Board (Box 66)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 66)
    - Virginia Cattlemen's Association (Box 66)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 66)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 66)
    - NASDA (3) (Box 66)
    - NASDA (2) (Box 66)
    - NASDA (1) (Box 66)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 66)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (Box 66)
    - VPI and SU (Box 66)
    - Warrenton Laboratory (Box 66)
    - Warner, John (Senator) (Box 66)
    - Worker Protection Standard (Box 66)
  - 1996
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry (Box 67)
    - Disasters (Box 67)
    - Eastern Shore Farmers Market (Box 67)
    - Eastern Shore Marketing Cooperative (Box 67)
    - E-Coli (Box 67)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Egg Council (Box 67)
    - EEO Committee (Box 67)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - US Environmental Protection Agency (Box 67)
    - Farm Bill (Box 67)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation (Box 67)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 67)
    - Forestry, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 67)
    - Friends of the Industry of Agriculture (Box 67)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Goats Milk (Box 67)
    - Governor's Office (Box 67)
    - Grievance Procedures (Box 67)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - HJR 45 Rural Economic Development Plan (Box 67)
    - HJR 221 (Box 67)
    - HJR 699 (Box 67)
    - Hong Kong Office (Box 67)
    - Virginia Horse Council (Box 67)
    - House of Representatives (US) (Box 67)
    - Human Investigator Advisory Commission (Box 67)
    - Impact Assessment (Box 67)
    - Inclement Weather Policy (Box 67)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 67)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 67)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 67)
    - Internet (Box 67)
    - James City County Growers Cooperative (Box 67)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee (JLARC) (Box 67)
    - Karnal Bunt (Box 68)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Lake Anna Advisory Committee (Box 68)
    - Land Use (Box 68)
    - Legislative Automated Systems, Division of (Box 68)
    - 1996 Federal Legislative Goals, Congressional Delegation Briefing (Box 68)
    - Agency Legislative Package, 1996 (Box 68)
    - Proposed Legislation 1997 (Box 68)
    - 1996 Legislative Proposals (Box 68)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Legislation (Box 68)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 68)
    - Federal Mandates (Box 68)
    - Market Promotion Program (MPP) (Box 68)
    - Metrology Laboratory (Box 68)
    - Virginia Milk Commission (Box 68)
    - Minority Business Enterprises, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Mode General Assembly - YMCA (Box 68)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Northern Neck Virginia Farmers' Market (Box 68)
    - Virginia's "Open for Agribusiness" (Box 68)
    - Opportunity Virginia (Box 68)
    - Oxygenated Fuel (Box 68)
    - Performance Measures (Box 68)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Pesticide Disposal Program (Box 68)
    - Pesticide Groundwater Management (Box 68)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 68)
    - Virginia Plant Pollination Advisory Board (Box 68)
    - Plasti-Culture (Box 68)
    - Plastic Pesticide Container Recycling (Box 68)
    - Plastic Pesticide Container Recycling - Agreements (Box 68)
    - Potato Blight (Box 68)
    - Poultry Exports to Russia (Box 69)
    - Privatization/Competition Information Survey (Box 69)
    - Prompt Payment (Box 69)
    - Pseudorabies (Box 69)
    - Purcell, John B. (Box 69)
    - Rocco (Box 69)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program (REAP) (Box 69)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 69)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 69)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources (Box 69)
    - Seed Lab (Box 69)
    - Senators (Box 69)
    - Virginia Sheep Industry Board (Box 69)
    - Small Grains Board (Box 69)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 69)
    - Sole Source (Box 69)
    - Southern States (Box 69)
    - Soy Ink (Box 69)
    - Space Needs (Box 69)
    - State Fair (Box 69)
    - State Technical Committee (Box 69)
    - Stationary (Box 69)
    - Synar Amendment (Box 69)
    - Strategic Planning 1996 (1) (Box 69)
    - Strategic Planning 1996 (2) (Box 69)
    - Strategic Planning 1996 (3) (Box 69)
    - Task Force on Food Safety (Box 69)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 69)
    - TB Status (Box 69)
    - Tobacco (Box 69)
    - Tobacco Warehouse (Box 69)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 69)
    - Travel (Blanket Approval) (Box 69)
    - Treasury, Dept. of (Box 69)
    - USDA (3) (Box 69)
    - USDA (2) (Box 69)
    - USDA (1) (Box 69)
    - Voice Mail (Box 69)
    - VPI and SU (Box 70)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 70)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council (Box 70)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 70)
    - Virginia Cattle Industry Board (Box 70)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 70)
    - Virginia-Maryland-Delaware Poultry (Box 70)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 70)
    - NASDA Policies 1996 (Box 70)
    - NASDA (3) (Box 70)
    - NASDA (2) (Box 70)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 70)
    - Palmer, Terri A. (Box 70)
    - NASDA Resolutions (Box 70)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 70)
    - SASDA (Box 70)
    - NASDA (1) (Box 70)
    - SUSTA (Box 70)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 70)
    - Waters, Mary Ann, Director, Communication and Media Relations (Box 70)
  - 1997
    - NASDA Policy Statements (Box 71)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 71)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 71)
    - SASDA (Box 71)
    - SUSTA (Box 71)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Adv. Board (Box 71)
    - Governor's Fellows Program (Box 71)
    - Governor's Office (Box 71)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Virginia Horse Center (Box 71)
    - Virginia Horse Council (Box 71)
    - House of Representatives (US Congress) (Box 71)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 71)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Information Technology Adv. Group (Box 71)
    - Interior, Dept. of (US) (Box 71)
    - Interstate Milk Shipper (Box 71)
    - James City County Growers Cooperative (Box 71)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Council (JLARC) (Box 71)
    - Karnal Bunt (Box 71)
    - Labor and Industry, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Lan Expansion Meeting, November 1997 (Box 71)
    - Land Use (Box 71)
    - Leadership/Management Development Program (Box 71)
    - Legislative Automated Systems, Division of (Box 71)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Virginia Liaison Office (Box 71)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 71)
    - Logo (International Marketing) (Box 71)
    - Mandates - Federal (Box 71)
    - Metrology Laboratory (Box 71)
    - Virginia Milk Commission (Box 71)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Milk Producers Case - Minnesota (Box 71)
    - Model General Assembly - YMCA (Box 71)
    - NAFTA (Box 71)
    - Northern Neck Virginia Farmers Market (Box 71)
    - Virginia Nurserymen's Association (Box 71)
    - Virginia's Open for Agribusiness (Box 71)
    - Performance Measures (Box 71)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Pfiesteria (Box 71)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 71)
    - Virginia Plant Pollination Advisory Board (Box 71)
    - Pork Production (Box 71)
    - Poultry Exports to Russia (Box 71)
    - Right to Farm Act (Box 71)
    - Resolutions - Study, 1997 (Box 71)
    - Savings Bond Campaign (Box 71)
    - Scrapie (Box 71)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 71)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources (Box 71)
    - Senate Finance (Box 71)
    - Senate Resolution No. 29 (Box 71)
    - Senators (Box 71)
    - Service Regions - VDACS (Box 71)
    - Virginia Sheep Industry Board (Box 71)
    - Small Grains Board (Box 71)
    - Smyth Food Service (Box 71)
    - Soil and Water Conservation (Box 72)
    - Sole Source (Box 72)
    - Southern States (Box 72)
    - Space Needs (Box 72)
    - State Fair (Box 72)
    - State Technical Committee (Box 72)
    - Virginia State University (Box 72)
    - Strategic Planning (Box 72)
    - Task Force on Food Safety (Box 72)
    - Task Force on Plasticulture (Box 72)
    - Task Force on Virginia Agriculture Education (Box 72)
    - Virginia Seafood Marketing Task Force (Box 72)
    - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 72)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 72)
    - Tobacco (Box 72)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 72)
    - Travel (Box 72)
    - Travel - Blanket (Box 72)
    - Travel Authorization Forms for Boards (Box 72)
    - USDA (1) (Box 72)
    - USDA (2) (Box 72)
  - 1998
    - USDA (1) (Box 73)
    - USDA (2) (Box 73)
    - USDA (3) (Box 73)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (Box 73)
    - VPI and SU (Box 73)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 73)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council (Box 73)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 73)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 73)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 73)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 73)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 73)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 73)
    - NASDA (1) (Box 73)
    - NASDA (2) (Box 73)
    - SASDA (Box 73)
    - SUSTA (Box 73)
    - EPA Poultry Industry Proposal (1) (Box 74)
    - EPA Poultry Industry Proposal (2) (Box 74)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (US) (Box 74)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 74)
    - Service Contracts - Extended (Box 74)
    - Farm Building Study Advisory Committee (Box 74)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, Virginia (Box 74)